레볼루션
지난 이야기
Previously on "Revolution":
- 먼로시죠
- 던컨은 어딨어?
- You Monroe?
- Where's Duncan?
- 죽었어요
- 어쩌다가?
- She's dead.
- How?
애국자들 때문에요
복수를 원해요
Patriots. And we want blood.
We're moving out!
움직입시다!
마일스를 기다리자
Bass! Wait for Miles.
원하는 건 다 얻었어
I got the men I need, Rachel.
더 이상 말 들을
필요 없다고
Don't have to listen to you anymore.
I don't want to lose you, Aaron.
당신을 잃기 싫어
Me neither.
나도
숫자를 말하면
I say that number,
내가 시키는 건
뭐든지 하지
and he does anything I say, anything.
도일 말이 사실이면...
Dad, if what he said is true...
번역을 완료했는데
이것 좀 보세요
My guy translated this. You need to see it.
생도들이 어딨는진
알게 됐네...
At least we know where
they're taking the cadets...
오스틴에 있어
텍사스 무너트리고
to Austin, to take down
the, uh, Texas government
대통령을 죽이려고
and kill their president.
어디 있었니?
Where you been?
여기요
Right here.
Well...
할 일이 있다
We got work to do.
먼로를 찾아내야지
Still got to track Monroe.
어서 움직이자
So let's get to it.
싫어요
No.
싫다니 뭔 소리냐?
What do you mean no?
싫어요
No.
어떤 짓을 했는지
신경이나 쓰이세요?
Do you even care what they've done to me?
They made me do... God knows...
놈들이 절...
기억조차 안 나요
What. I... I don't remember.
또 어떻게 될지
누가 알아요?
Who knows what else
they can make me do, dad?
두렵다고요
It scares the hell out of me.
이럴 시간 없다
We don't have time for this. Come on.
그냥 남자답게
참고 견디라고요?
What, you want me to walk it off?
Want me to tough it out?
그래, 내가
그렇게 키웠잖니
Actually, yes. That's how I raised you.
네 엄마를 구하려면
먼로를 죽여야 해
You want to save your
mother, we kill Monroe.
That's it.
엄마는 죽었어요
Mom is dead.
입 조심해라
Don't you say that.
유감이지만
I'm sorry.
그게 사실이예요
I am, but it's true.
절대 돌려주지
않을 거예요
They're never gonna give her back to you.
거짓말한 거라고요
They're lying to you.
거짓말인 거 알잖아요
You're lying to yourself. But I'm here!
전 여기 있어요!
바로 앞에서
I'm right in front of you.
도움을 청하잖아요
And I'm asking for your help.
아들아...
Son...
힘든 거 안단다
I know this hasn't been easy for you.
조금만 더 참고 견디렴
You just need to hold it together
for a little while longer.
돌아와
Get back here.
떠나지 마라
Don't you walk away from me.
당장 돌아와!
Get back here!
책 번역했다면서
You said your guy could translate this.
이게 전부야?
This is all he got?
생도들이 오스틴에서
The cadets are heading to Austin,
텍사스 정부를
무너트리려고 해요
Texas government's on the chopping block.
멋진 계획이네
At least we've got a great plan.
오스틴 주위를
정처 없이 맴돌면서
We'll just wander around Austin aimlessly
테러 부대를
찾으면 되겠어
till we see some suicide bombers.
아무 문제 없겠다
I don't see what could go wrong.
번역 맘에 안 들어요?
You want to translate it yourself, pal...
직접 해보시던가
Have at it.
이게 장난 같냐?
You think this is a game?
애국자들이 텍사스를
잡으면 끝이야
Patriots take Texas, that's it. It's over.
놈들을 막을 만한
군대는 더 없어
There'll be nobody else
around big enough to stop 'em.
그런데 우리 보다
사흘이나 앞서 있지
And now they're three days
ahead of us on the road.
- 제이슨?
- 보내줘
- Jason?
- Let him go.
보내달라고
Let him go!
I said, "Let him go."
문을 통과하려면
이 방법 밖에 없었어요
Sorry. This was the only
way to get through the door.
당신들을 돕고 싶어요
But I want to help you.
우릴 돕고 싶다고?
You want to help us?
어떻게?
How?
트루먼 사무실에서
가져온 거예요
Intel from Truman's office.
정말?
Really?
애비는 뭐라더냐?
How's your dad feel about that?
신경 안 써요
I could care less.
생도들을
오스틴으로 보냈어요
They sent cadets to Austin.
이유는 모르지만
아넬 19번가로요
I don't know why, but they're
headed to 19 Arnell Street.
왜 알려주는 거지?
Why are you telling us this?
뭔 짓을 하려고 하든
Because whatever they're gonna do,
같이 가서 놈들을
막고 싶어요
I need to come with you, and
I want to help you stop 'em.
장난하냐?
Are you joking?
우릴 그렇게 배신했잖아
After all the times you screwed us over.
맞는 말이네
She's got a great point.
나도 알아요
Yeah, I know she does.
되도록 안 믿는 게
좋을 거예요
And right now I'm about the last guy
you should be trusting.
이게 뭔지 알아요?
You have any idea what that is?
그래
Yeah.
본 적 있어
We've seen one or two of 'em.
그 개자식들이
이런 거예요...
That's what those sons
of bitches did to me...
더 끔직한 짓들도요
that and a lot more.
저도 그동안
망쳤단 거 알아요
Look, I know I got nothing
here, nothing but burned bridges.
받아줘야 할
이유가 없는 것도요
And I know there's no
reason for you to take me,
부탁할게요
but I'm asking.
도울 수 있어요
And I can help.
복수를 원해요
I need payback.
속임수가 아니란 걸
어떻게 알지?
And how do we know this isn't a trick?
이미 최면 상태에
빠진 걸 수도 있잖아?
How do we know you're
not zombified right now?
모르죠
You don't.
제가 조금이라도
허튼짓하면
But if I step out of line just an inch,
쏴버려요
shoot me.
정말로요?
Seriously?
받아줄 생각은 아니겠죠?
Are you actually considering this?
유용할 거야
Well, this kid could come in handy.
말한 대로
And it's like he said,
조금이라도 허튼짓하면
쏴버리자고
he makes one wrong move, we shoot him.
우리말 번역: 후룰루꾸
Revolution S02E18
Austin City Limits
진은 어때?
How's your dad?
의사들은 형편없는
환자라는 거 알아?
You know how they say
doctor's make the crappiest patients?
괜찮아
He's all right.
다 나으려면
며칠 정도 걸려
Just needs a couple days to heal.
정말 오기 싫어?
Sure you don't want to come?
생도들 찾으면
어떻게 할 거야?
What are you gonna do with
the cadets when you find them?
찰리 잘 부탁해
먼로 조심하고
Take care, Charlie. Watch out for Monroe.
걱정하지 마
Ah, buck up, tiger.
이틀 뒤면 다시
족쇄에 묶일 텐데 뭐
You can do 72 hours
without the ball and chain.
남자들만의 주말이잖아
This is a boys' weekend.
신 나게 놀아보자고
We're gonna have ourselves some fun.
이랴!
Get up!
50 마일 밖
텍사스 윌러비
냄새 좋은걸
Something smells good.
좋은 아침
Morning.
차 마실래?
I'm making tea. You want some?
텍사스 오스틴
저 덩치 친구랑
얽힌 게 있나 본데
You and six-pack make
quite the spicy team.
사연이 어떻게 돼?
So what kind of number did he do on you?
이 세상에서 제일
못 미더운 사람이
Well, the only person in the world
I trust less than him is you.
쟤 다음 너야
아넬 19번가
생에 첫 총이구나
A boy never forgets his first firearm.
생일 축하한다
Happy Birthday, kid.
안녕하세요
뭐 물어봐도 되나요?
Hi. Can I ask you something?
돈 내는 고객님은 되죠
A paying customer can.
육포 하나 주세요
Okay. I'll have some
of that jerky, I guess.
근처에서 저희 또래
애들 못 보셨나요?
You seen a couple of kids from out of town
over the past few days, about our age?
- 그쪽은 누구지?
- 친구들이에요
- And who's asking?
- They're friends of ours.
여기서 보기로 했거든요
We're supposed to meet them here.
위층에 있는
게으름 뱅이 친구한테
Well, then... you tell your
deadbeat friends upstairs
밤에 소리 좀
그만 내라고 해라
to stop making noise all night
밀린 방세도 좀 내고
and pay up on the rent they owe me.
감사합니다
Thank you.
내가 알아요
I know their playbook.
문 뒤에 함정을
설치해 놨을 거예요
If they don't blow our
heads off when we come in,
문 옆엔 철사랑
there's a trip wire connected to the door,
바닥엔 압력 수류탄이요
and two pressure grenades
under the floorboards.
수류탄은 여기 있어요
The grenades are here.
꽝!
Boom.
데리고 오길 잘했네
The kid's paying off already.
아랍어도 가르쳐줬냐?
I don't suppose they taught you any Arabic.
글자가 찢어졌어요
Word's cut off.
블랜치...
But it says... "Blanch. Blanch"
블랜치?
"Blan... Blanch"?
블랜차드
Blanchard.
- 블랜차드를 공격할 거야
- 누구요?
- They're gonna hit Blanchard.
- Who?
텍사스 전 지도자야
He's the former leader of
this ten-gallon craphole.
우릴 좋아하진 않지
Not a fan of ours.
보자마자 죽일걸
He's gonna want to shoot us on sight.
그럴지도
Yeah, maybe.
아니면...
Or maybe...
우리가 도와주면
우릴 도와줄지도
we help him out, he helps us out.
벌써 죽지 않았다면
That's if he's not dead already.
가자
Come on.
여기 남아서
도움될 거 찾아봐
You stay here, see what else you can find.
이상하게 쳐다보면
쏴버려
If he even looks at you funny, shoot him.
Stop?
그만?
아우! 젠장!
Ow! Whoa, whoa! Damn!
오우! 호두!
Oh! Walnut!
아우! 호두!
Ow! Walnut!
워우! 호두!
Whoa, whoa! Walnut, walnut!
미안, 프랭크
Sorry, Frank.
소용 없어
Your safe words are no good here.
일 쉽게 만들어줘서
정말 고마워
I got to tell you, Frank,
you're making this way too easy.
잠깐만
넌 죽었잖아!
Hang on. You're supposed to be dead!
날 원하는
사람이 좀 많거든
Back by popular demand.
믿을 수가 없군
Oh, I don't believe this.
날 죽이러 온 거야?
You two are here to
kill me? Are you serious?
나 퇴역했다고!
I mean, hell, I'm retired!
그래서 온 게 아냐
Yeah, that's not why we're here.
널 죽이려는 건
우리가 아니야
I mean, we're not the
ones trying to kill you.
뭐야?
What do you got?
캘리포니아 신분증
California papers.
애국자들이 캘리포니아
신분증은 뭣 하러?
What the hell are Patriots doing
with I.D.s from California?
제이슨!
Jason!
너 이새끼!
It's you!
그만! 그러다 죽겠어!
Stop! Stop! You're gonna kill him!
그만!
Stop!
누구야?
Who is that?
질문 좀 해도 돼?
Can I ask you a question if
you promise not to get mad?
물론
Sure.
그게...
Well, it's just...
가족들 얘길 안 하는데...
you haven't mentioned your...
family in, like, forever.
그립지 않아?
Don't you miss them?
물론 그립지
Of course I miss them.
가슴이 아파
It just hurts.
찾고 싶으면...
Well, if you want to look for them...
내가 도와줄게
I will help you.
고마워
Thank you.
- 숨어
- 뭐?
- Hide.
- What?
당장
Hide, now.
노예 상인
Slavers.
어떻게 알았어?
How did you know anyone was coming?
소릴 들었지
못 들었어?
I heard them. You didn't?
그래
No.
당신 거 맞지?
Thought this was yours.
거물을 오스틴으로
보낸 건가?
Sending in the big guns to Austin.
돌아버리겠네
누구냐니까?
Jason, for the 100th time, who is this guy?
그래, 제이슨
Yeah, Jason.
내가 누군지 말해줘
Tell 'em who I am.
여기 이 친구는...
Your buddy here was a...
최우수 생도야
Gold star cadet.
훈련생을 많이 봤지만
제이슨은...
I trained a lot of 'em, but Jason...
항상 놀라웠지
they broke the mold with you.
엄청난 애국자가
됐을 텐데 말이야
You'd have made a hell of a Patriot.
다른 생도들은?
Where are the cadets?
누굴 공격하지?
Who are they gonna hit?
생도 애들이랑
다른 게 뭔지 알아?
You want to know the thing
that really sets you apart?
싸움에 쉽게 빠져들어
It was how fast the fight
went out of you.
과할 정도로
내 말은...
I mean, you gave in...
무도회에 뚱녀랑
가는 것 보다도 쉽게
rasier than a fat girl on prom night.
생도들 어딨는지
당장 불어
You're gonna tell me where
the cadets are right now.
아니면 이렇게 하지
Or I got another idea.
내가 숫자를 말하고
How about I read you your number,
네가 일을 대신하는 거야
and you can do their jobs for them?
숫자를 알았다면
이미 말했겠지
If you knew my number,
you'd have already said it.
말 되는군
That is a fair point.
어쨌거나 네 본성을
바꾸지는 않아...
Either way, it doesn't
change what you are...
멍청하고 순종적이고
낮은 자존심에
dumb, obedient, with low self-esteem.
내가 좋아하던 대로
That's just how I like 'em.
애비가 교육을
아주 잘 시켰구나
Yo' daddy... he must've raise you right.
대체 어딨냐고?
Where are they? Where the hell are they?
친구들도 못 믿어서
Even your friends don't trust you.
수갑을 채워놨잖아
That's why they got you cuffed...
얼마나 위험한지
알기 때문이야
'cause they know how dangerous you are.
넌 그냥 망치 같은
You're nothing but a hammer, man.
무딘 무기에 불과해
You're a dull, blunt weapon.
그게 전부라고
It's all you're ever gonna be.
왜 거부하는지 모르겠다
I don't even know why you fight it.
뭘 하려는지 알아
I know what you're trying to do.
화나게 만들어서
You're trying to make me fly off the handle
입 열기 전에
죽이게 하려는 거잖아
so I kill you before you talk.
소용 없을 거야
But it's not gonna work.
나에 관해선 틀렸어
And you're wrong about me.
명령받는 건 질렸어
I'm done taking orders...
당신한테서든 누구든
from you, from anyone.
한 가진 맞췄어
But you're right about one thing.
난 최우수 학생이야
I am a grade-A student.
최고한테서 배웠으니까
And I've learned from the best.
수갑 풀어줘
Uncuff me.
찰리
Charlie...
지금 실수하는 거야
Sweetheart, you're making a big mistake.
제이슨을 믿어
I trust him.
시작해보자고
Let's get started.
우릴 믿어줘서 놀랐어
I got to say, Frank, I'm
surprised you believe us.
괜찮으면...
Do you mind...
옷 좀 입을래?
Shutting the gate?
널 믿어
I believe you.
이야기를 꾸며낼 만큼
똑똑하지도 않고
One, you two ain't smart enough
to make up a story that nuts.
내 의심을 확인시켜줬잖아
And two, you're just confirming
my suspicions, is all.
그래? 어떻게?
Yeah? How's that?
아가씨들
Ladies...
자리 좀?
If you wouldn't mind.
늙은 변태 자식
You're a dirty old man, Frank.
누가 늙었대?
Who you calling "old"?
어쨌거나 지난밤에
So, anyway, just last night,
상원 의원 웨이먼이
총에 맞았어
senator wymann got popped.
부하가 저격범을
몰아 붙었는데
Now, wymann's men cornered the shooter.
왠 애더라고
It was some kid.
총을 머리에 갖다 대더니
Little bastard looked right at 'em.
빵! 쏴버렸다니까
Boom! Blew his own brains out.
캘리포니아 신분증을
갖고 있었지
Boy was carrying California paper.
주지사 애플렉이
Now, I know Governor Affleck
남편이 요절한 뒤로
달라졌다지만...
ain't been right since her husband died,
but...
그녀가 이런 짓을
꾸몄다는 건 말도 안 돼
it don't make sense for her
to pull a move like that.
안 그랬으니까
That's 'cause she didn't.
캘리포니아에서 보냈다고
믿게 하려는 속셈이지
They wanted you to think
the kid was from California.
놈은 애국자야
The kid's a Patriot.
서로 전쟁을 붙여서
They're gonna get you
and Cali all riled up.
치고박고 하는 동안
You're gonna rip each other's throats out.
틈을 파고들어
뒷처리를 하겠지
They're gonna waltz in, clean up the mess.
조지아 때의 일처럼
It's pretty much what they
did with me and Georgia.
지금까진 잘 풀렸지
So far, it's working.
상원 의원들 절반이
Half our Senate's screaming for the scalps
벌써부터 지랄들이야
of these yoga-monkeys.
악의는 없는데...
And... no offense...
왜 너야?
but why target you?
퇴역했잖아?
I mean, aren't you out to pasture?
미국 새끼들을
안 믿으니까 그렇지
Because I don't trust those U.S. bastards.
내가 떠들고 다녔어
And I've been loud about it.
더는 혼자만의
의심이 아니지
Now... now it ain't just my hot air.
이젠 증명할 수 있어
Now we got facts.
어떻게 하려고?
So what's the play?
카버한테 가서
I'll pay Carver a visit
재수 없는 얼굴에
한 방 먹여줘야지
and kick some sense into his scrawny ass.
아직도 높은 곳에
친구들이 많아
And I still got a lot of
friends in the right places.
일이 끝났을 쯤엔
By the time I'm done,
all of Texas will be out
애국자 새끼들
피로 가득할 거야
for some red, white, and blue blood.
그 애국자 새끼들은
Those Patriot sons of bitches
텍사스 사람을
잘못 건드린 거야
have screwed with the wrong Texan.
우리가 바라던 게
바로 그거야
Thank you. That is what I'm talking about.
내가 더 고맙지
Believe me, it's my pleasure.
현역으로 뛸 수 있잖아
It'd be good to be in action again.
쉬는 것도 질렸어
Retirement sucks.
여기 건배나 하지
Here's to getting back in that chair.
할 일이 많아
We got a lot of work to do.
바지나 좀 입어야겠군
I guess I should put on some pants.
Hmm?
뭐야?
What? What?
진심이야?
Are you serious, Miles?
일이 술술 풀리잖아?
You can't even tell when
things are going your way?
솔직히 말해서
Please tell me this is better
레이첼이랑 쿵짝하던
때보다 훨씬 좋잖아
than the pity party you got
back there with Rachel, huh?
너네 둘 진짜...
You two are like the...
시드와 낸시 같았다니까
Sid and Nancy of frowning.
무슨 소리야?
What does that mean?
내가 알던 남자는...
It means the guy that I know...
모든 결정들을
스스로 내리고
didn't used to sit
around wringing his hands
over every decision.
이기기 위해선
뭐든지 했었다고
He used to go in there and
do what he had to do to win.
지금의 넌...
But you, I mean, look...
수족관에 갇힌
범고래 같단 말이야
it's like watching a
killer whale at Seaworld.
한심하긴
Pathetic.
끝났냐?
You done?
레이첼이 이렇게
만들어 놨구나
Rachel did this to you.
그만해
All right, ju... stop.
어쩌면 네 생각만큼
날 잘 모르나 보지
Maybe you don't know me as
well as you think you do.
아니면 너 자신보다
잘 아는 걸지도
Or maybe I know you better
than you know yourself.
안 돼!
No!
숫자가 적혀 있어
윌러비에서 온 거야
She's got the tattoo. She's
from the Willoughby camp.
- 왜 몰랐어?
- 얼굴을 못 봤어
You didn't recognize her? I
wasn't looking at her face.
이봐!
Hey!
우리 짓이 아니라면
믿어 주겠어?
What if I told you this
is not what it looks like?
세바스찬 먼로잖아
총 내려놔
You're Sebastian Monroe. You drop the gun.
내려놓으라고!
I said drop it!
당장!
Now!
누구야?
What'd we miss?
생도 훈련관이요
He's the cadet handler.
다음 타켓은
카버 장군이에요
Their next target's General Carver.
한 시에 의사당에서
공격할 거예요
They're gonna hit him
at the Capitol building,
1:00 today.
그러도록 놔두자고
We're letting that one happen.
대통령이잖아
Bass, he's the president.
죽으면 캘리포니아가
독박 쓸테고...
They kill him, frame California...
날 죽이려던 놈이잖아
이해 좀 해줘
He had me executed, all right?
Excuse me if I hold a grudge.
잘했다
Nice work, kid.
수갑 채워도 돼요
You can cuff me again if you want.
아냐, 됐어
No, you're good.
먼로가 살아있다니?
What do you mean Monroe's alive?
죽는 걸 지켜봤잖아
We watched him die.
제가 직접 묻었어요
I put him in the ground myself.
부하 놈이 직접
두 눈으로 봤답니다
But I'm telling you, the
ranger who laid eyes on him
is reliable and sober.
블랜차드는?
And General Blanchard?
의사가 노력하고 있어요
Doctors are doing the best they can.
최근 암살시도와
Sir, with the recent assassinations
먼로를 고려해서
and now with Monroe here,
일정을 변경하시는 게?
I suggest we reschedule.
난 빌어먹을
텍사스 대통령이야
I'm the leader of the Texas Republic.
일정변경 따윈 없어
I'm not gonna reschedule.
경비 3배로 늘리고
Triple security, put
every man on the ground.
일이나 해
Do your job.
먼로를 찾아서
Find Monroe.
이번엔 확실히 죽여
And this time, make sure he stays dead.
제이슨
Hey.
놈이 한 말들...
What that guy said about you...
틀렸어
He's wrong.
넌 무기가 아니야
You're not just some weapon.
계획은 뭐예요
So what's the plan?
눈 똑바로 뜨고
윌러비 애들 찾아야지
Keep our eyes open, look
for kids from Willoughby.
너무 늦지 않게
Hope we catch a break.
대체 왜 그래?
What the hell is going on?
무슨 소리야?
What do you mean?
계속 보고 있었는데
I mean, I've been watching you.
밤새 잠 안 잤잖아
You didn't sleep all night.
- 그렇지 않아
- 맞아
- That's not true.
- Yes, it is.
지난 45분 동안
눈도 안 깜박였어
I'm pretty sure you haven't blinked
in the last 45 minutes,
애들 생각도 안 하고
and you don't seem to care about your kids,
어젯밤에 마차 소리를
들었을 리도 없어
and there is no way you
heard that wagon last night.
분명히 들었어
I heard that wagon.
어떻게 감히 아이들
얘기를 꺼내?
And how dare you say that about my kids?
그만해!
Stop it! Just...
그만
Just stop.
넌 그녀가 아니야
You're not her, are you?
뭐라고?
Wha... what?
말도 안 돼는 소리야
Aaron, that's crazy.
너 나노지?
You're the nano.
어떻게 설명하지?
How would you say it?
프리실라 몸에
잠시 머물고 있어
We're behind Priscilla's
wheel for the moment.
- 그녀를 돌려놔
- 애런...
- Give her back to me...
- Aaron...
당장
- Now.
- Just...
- 당장 돌려놔!
- 진정해
- Give her back to me now!
- Calm down.
무슨 짓을 한 거야?
What did you do with her?
머릿속에 갇혔을 때 기억나?
Remember when we were inside your head?
2014년에 아름다웠지
You were in 2014, and it was wonderful,
받아 들이지 않고
but you wouldn't accept it.
계속 저항했잖아
You just kept rebelling.
프리실라도 거기에 있어
Well, we were inside Priscilla's head too,
거부하지 않아
but she didn't fight it.
행복해하지
She's happier.
여기에 있어
She's in here,
딸들한테 빵 구워주면서
making French toast for her girls.
헤치진 않을 거야
We won't hurt her.
몸을 잠깐 빌릴 뿐이야
We just want to use her
body for a little while.
왜?
Why?
사과가 얼마나
맛있는지 듣는 것과
It's one thing to hear
what an apple tastes like.
실제로 맛보는 건 다르거든
It's another to actually taste one.
사람들이 섹스에
It's one thing to hear
정신 팔린걸 보는 거랑
how much you people are
preoccupied with sex.
진짜로 해보는 건 달라
It's another to actually have it.
그나저나 좋았어
It was nice, by the way.
배우고 싶어...
We want to learn...
인간이 되는걸
how to be human.
그게 다야
That's all.
뭘 위해서?
What for?
내 말대로만 하면
프리실라를 돌려줄게
Just do what we say, and
you will get Priscilla back.
그동안 우릴 안내해줘
In the meantime, you will be our guide,
아무한테도 말하지 말고
and you won't tell anyone.
거부한다면?
And if I refuse?
신사 숙녀 여러분
국가의 아버지
Ladies and gentlemen, without
further ado, the state of the nation!
이미 늦은듯싶다
Well, so much for catching a break.
빌 카버 장군!
General Bill Carver!
수퍼볼에서 바늘찾기네
It's gonna be like trying to
find a needle at the Super Bowl.
- 새 계획 있어요?
- 아니
- So is there a new plan?
- No.
생도들 찾으면
그냥... 쏴버려
You see any kids from
Willoughby, sh... shoot 'em.
흩어져서 찾아봐
Let's just split up and look.
텍사스 윌러비
캠프를 몇 번이나
공격한 거예요?
How many camps you hit this week?
- 4번이요
- 그래요?
- Four and counting, Ma'am.
- Yeah?
인정해야겠네요
친구분들이...
I got to hand it to you, you boys are...
효과적이네요
effective.
멍청해서 안타깝네요
It's too bad you're so stupid.
- 뭐라고요?
- 먼로를 따르다니
- Excuse me?
- Following Monroe.
저만큼 놈을 모르잖아요
You don't know him like I do.
당신을 어디로
이끄는지 알아요?
The only place he's going to lead you...
무덤 속이에요
is into a grave.
레이첼!
Rachel!
총 내려놔요!
Hey! Put your weapons down!
친구예요
They're friends. Please.
애런?
Aaron?
반갑다
Hi!
여기서...
What are you, uh...
무서운 친구들이랑
여기서 뭐하는 거야?
What are you doing in a
hellhole with a bunch of bikers?
이야기가 좀 길어
Long story.
어떻게 찾았어?
How did you find me?
프리실라 기억하지?
Uh, you remember Priscilla?
널 찾아냈어
그런 거에 뛰어나거든
She tracked you. She's, uh, good at it.
반가워요
It's good to see you.
저도 반가워요, 레이첼
It's good to see you too, Rachel.
It's what separated us
from the other 49 states.
They knew it.
And although they had a
hard time admitting it,
they respected it.
Those values are what led us
대정전에서 살아남았고
to not only survive the blackout,
전보다도 번창했죠
but thrive despite it.
괜찮아
It's all right, buddy. I got you.
커피 좀 마시자
Let's get you some coffee.
어디 가니, 제이슨?
Hang on. Where you going, Jason?
4-2-4-7-4
4-2-4-7-4.
지휘관 셜리 젠킨스다
This is Commanding Officer Shirlee Jenkins.
마을에 왔을 때부터
알아봤었다, 생도
I've had an eye on you since
you came to town, cadet.
누구랑 같이 왔지?
Tell me who you're here with.
마일스 매더슨과
세바스찬 먼로요
Miles Matheson and Sebastian Monroe.
카버 암살을
막으려 해요
They're here to stop
the Carver assassination.
좋아...
All right, then...
가방 이리 줘
Take the bag.
네가 대신해라
You're our backup.
Jason.
제이슨
올해 텍사스 레인저
신입생들입니다!
The incoming class of
this year's Texas rangers!
명예, 정의, 용기, 힘
Honor, justice, courage, strength...
텍사스의 진정한 아들들이여
you are all the true sons of Texas.
너희들이 우리를 대변한다
You represent the very best of all of us.
제이슨?
Jason?
여기서 뭐해?
What are you doing up here?
Better vantage point. Spotted
a kid... he's got a gun.
감시하기 좋은 위치야
생도를 발견했어
어디?
Where?
저기
There.
5분 동안 안 움직여
He hasn't moved in five minutes.
가서 확인해봐
You should go check him out.
이게 뭐야?
What's this?
어디서 났어?
Where did you get this?
제이슨, 멈춰!
Jason, stop!
멈추라고!
Stop!
그만해!
제발... 그만
Please... S... stop.
이건 네가 아니야
This isn't you.
떨쳐내
Snap out of it.
Congratulations.
축하한다
제발, 돌아와 줘
Please, this isn't you.
제이슨
Jason.
물러서!
Stay back! Stay back. Stay back.
부탁할게 물러서...
Jason, I'm begging you. Please stay...
Take cover, everyone! Get down!
우리말 번역: 후룰루꾸
- synced and corrected by chamallow -
- www.addic7ed.com -